landstaronline.com 2003-06-10

# Landstar Privacy Policy

**Landstar's Privacy Policy**

This site is owned and operated by Landstar System, Inc. and contains material that is derived in whole or in part from information supplied to Landstar System, Inc. and its subsidiaries. You may not modify, copy, reproduce, republish, or distribute in any way, any material from this site, including any code, without prior written consent from the Corporate Communications department of Landstar System, Inc.

Landstar System, Inc. has provided links to Internet sites maintained by third parties. Neither Landstar System, Inc. or its subsidiary companies operate or control any information, products or services on these third-party sites.

Landstar System, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website.

**Security**

Our site's secured section requires users to give us unique identifiers such as their userid and password. Landstar System Inc. utilizes the latest technologies to provide secure transactions related to sensitive data on the site. Landstar System, Inc. does not distribute, free or for a charge, any personal information provided to us on this site. The information is reserved for Landstar System, Inc.’s exclusive use. The Landstar System, Inc. website uses multiple “cookies”. These exist in memory or on disk only for the duration of the browser session. The cookies are used to track browser session state, and related application information. No user information is stored in any cookies. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please send email to [CorpComm@Landstar.com](mailto:CorpComm@landstar.com?Subject=FROM-Landstar.com).
